Guide to the Yale College Records of Classes
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale College records of Classes
1803-2017
RU 491
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
47.26
(113 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, questionnaires, memoranda, log books, memorabilia, agendas, minutes and finanical reports from class council and executive council meetings, and statistical charts and reports of Yale College classes. Materials concerning the Sheffield Scientic School Class of 1920 are also included.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 10-A (YRG 10-A), Records of Yale College classes.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, questionnaires, memoranda, log books, memorabilia, agendas, minutes and finanical reports from class council and executive council meetings, and statistical charts and reports of Yale College classes. Materials concerning the Sheffield Scientic School Class of 1920 are also included.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1803; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1808; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1814; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1815; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1816; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1820; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1821; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1822; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1824; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1826; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1828; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1831; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1832; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1833; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1838; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1839; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1840; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1841; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1842; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1843; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1844; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1846; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1848; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1849; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1850; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1851; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1852; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1853; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1857; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1859; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1861; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1862; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1864; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1867; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1868; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1869; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1870; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1871; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1872; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1873; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1874; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1875; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1876; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1877; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1879; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1880; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1881; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1882; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1883; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1884; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1885; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1887; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1888; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1889; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1890; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1892; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1893; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1894; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1895; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1896; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1897; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1898; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1899; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1900; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1901; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1902; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1903; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1904; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1905; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1908; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1910; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1911; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1912; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1913; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1916; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1917; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1919; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1920; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1924; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1925; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1926; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1930; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1931; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1932; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1933; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1952; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale University. Sheffield Scientific School. Class of 1920
- Collected records of the Classes of 1803-1899, circa 1803-1964; Accession 1964-A-005
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - Class of 1803
    - Constitution, 1803 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1808
    - Correspondence, 1812-1868 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1814
    - Correspondence, 1844 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1815
    - Correspondence: notes of class meetings, 1845, 1865 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1816
    - Biographical notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1820
    - Reunion Committee, 20th: minutes of meeting and biographical notes, 1840, 1855 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1821
    - Class book: biographies, oratories, minutes of class of meeting, 1821 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1801-1879 (Box 1, Folder 8 - 15)
    - Correspondence: minutes of meeting, 1826-1866 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1822
    - Correspondence, 1828-1840 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1824
    - Correspondence, 1864-1874 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1826
    - Correspondence, 1870-1882 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1828
    - Correspondence; catalogue, 1878-1888 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1831
    - Correspondence; attendance and grade book, 1845-1891 (Box 2, Folder 21 - 33)
    - Miscellaneous: biographical sketches, tutor's notebook, correspondence, 1845-1856 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Class of 1832
    - Correspondence, 1828-1880 (Box 2, Folder 35 - 37)
    - Correspondence, 1828-1880 (Box 3, Folder 38 - 41)
    - Correspondence, 1832-1835 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence, 1880-1883 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence, 1879-1891 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Biographical Memoranda, 1880 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Class of 1833
    - Correspondence, 1883-1896 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Class of 1837
    - Notes of the class for the 40th reunion, 1879 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Class of 1838
    - Correspondence, 1868-1878 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence, 1864-1905 (Box 5, Folder 49 - 54)
    - Correspondence, 1864-1905 (Box 6, Folder 55 - 57)
  - Class of 1839
    - Correspondence, 1859-1866 (Box 7, Folder 58 - 60)
    - Class lists (compiled by H. A. Farr ca 1930s) (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Class of 1840
    - Correspondence, 1871-1896 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Class of 1841
    - Class book: secretary's record book, 1841 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Class of 1842
    - Class book: secretary's record book, 1842 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Correspondence, 1882-1883 (Box 7, Folder 65 - 66)
    - Correspondence, 1884-1887 (Box 8, Folder 67 - 72)
    - Correspondence, 1888-1891 (Box 9, Folder 73 - 80)
    - Correspondence, 1892-1895 (Box 10, Folder 81 - 85)
  - Class of 1843
    - Correspondence, 1873-1913 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Class of 1844
    - Correspondence, 1895-1910 (Box 11, Folder 87 - 92)
    - Correspondence, 1894-1898 (Box 12, Folder 93 - 95)
  - Class of 1845
    - Correspondence, 1861-1893 (Box 12, Folder 96 - 105)
  - Class of 1846
    - "Fifty years Progress" Hawley, David, 1896 (Box 13, Folder 106)
  - Class of 1848
    - Correspondence, 1848-1905 (Box 13, Folder 107)
  - Class of 1849
    - Correspondence, 1897, 1899 (Box 13, Folder 108)
  - Class of 1850
    - Correspondence, 1879-1895 (Box 13, Folder 109 - 113)
    - Correspondence, 1881-1886, 1910 (Box 13, Folder 114)
  - Class of 1851
    - Correspondence, 1891-1894 (Box 13, Folder 115)
  - Class of 1852
    - Notebook: memoranda, 1892 (Box 13, Folder 116)
  - Class of 1853
    - Notebook: lists of members attending reunions, meetings, 1853-1873 (Box 14, Folder 117)
    - Correspondence, 1858 (Box 14, Folder 118)
  - Class of 1857
    - Correspondence, 1887-1897 (Box 14, Folder 119)
    - Notebooks: meetings and statstics, 1857-1861 (Box 14, Folder 120)
  - Class of 1859
    - Sophomore year records (photostatic copies), 1857 (Box 14, Folder 121)
  - Class of 1861
    - Notebook: memoranda, 1861-1863 (Box 14, Folder 122)
  - Class of 1862
    - Correspondence, 1885-1892 (Box 15, Folder 123)
  - Class of 1864
    - History and memoranda, 1867-1884 (Box 15, Folder 124)
  - Class of 1867
    - Biographies of graduates, undated (Box 15, Folder 125 - 126)
    - Lists of students, 1863-1867 (Box 15, Folder 127)
    - Correspondence, 1873-1936 (Box 15, Folder 128 - 131)
    - Freshman Year Report, 1863 (Box 16, Folder 132)
    - History and membership, undated (Box 16, Folder 133)
    - Junior exhibition appointments, 1866 (Box 16, Folder 134)
    - Poems, songs, 1863, 1903, undated (Box 16, Folder 135)
    - Reunions: 3rd to 56th, 1870-1923 (Box 16, Folder 136)
    - Sophomore Biennial, 1865 (Box 16, Folder 137)
    - Statistics, 1867 (Box 16, Folder 138)
  - Class of 1868
    - Financial agreement to buy a geological specimen, 1869 (Box 16, Folder 139)
    - Notebooks: biographical notes, undated (Box 16, Folder 140)
  - Class of 1869 (Box 16)
    - Minutes, 1869 (Box 16, Folder 141)
  - Class of 1870
    - Notebook: Register, 1870 (Box 16, Folder 142)
    - Reunion photographs, 1870 (Box 16, Folder 142a)
  - Class of 1871
    - Correspondence, 1909-1934 (Box 17, Folder 143 - 147)
    - Correspondence, 1909-1934 (Box 18, Folder 148 - 153)
    - Correspondence, 1909-1934 (Box 19, Folder 154 - 158)
    - Receipted bills, 1914-1922 (Box 19, Folder 159)
    - Reunlon, 40th: memoranda, 1911 (Box 19, Folder 160)
    - Reunion, semi-centennial dinner, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 161)
    - Yale Alumni Weekly clippings, 1921-1929 (Box 19, Folder 162)
  - Class of 1872
    - History, 1872 (Box 20, Folder 163)
  - Class of 1873
    - Correspondence, 1909-1931 (Box 20, Folder 164 - 170)
    - Correspondence, 1909-1931 (Box 21, Folder 171 - 173)
    - Biographical material: notebook, undated (Box 22, Folder 174)
    - Miscellaneous: memoranda, lists, clippings, song, 1914-1929 (Box 22, Folder 175)
    - Reunion, 55th: Eighth Annual Dinner The Shaw Class Dinner Class Dinner, 1921, 1926-1927, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 176)
    - Sermons and speeches, 1910-1914, undated (Box 22, Folder 177)
    - The Survivor's Cup: deed of gift, 1908 (Box 22, Folder 178)
    - Yale Alumni Fund Association: correspondence, notebook, 1873-1932 (Box 22, Folder 179)
  - Class of 1874
    - Correspondence, 1894 (Box 23, Folder 180)
    - Biographical material, 1876-1877 (Box 23, Folder 181)
  - Class of 1875
    - Correspondence, 1910-33 (Box 23, Folder 182 - 183)
    - Miscellaneous memoranda, 1910-undated (Box 23, Folder 184)
    - Reunions, 38th, 40th, 45th, 50th, 55th: Correspondence and memoranda, 1911-1930 (Box 23, Folder 185)
  - Class of 1876
    - Correspondence, 1898-1910 (Box 24, Folder 186)
    - Correspondence, 1911-1928 (Box 24, Folder 187 - 192)
    - Correspondence, 1906-1937 (Box 25, Folder 193 - 198)
    - Biographical Information, 1911-1923 (Box 26, Folder 199)
    - Infomation for class record, 1916, 1921 (Box 26, Folder 200 - 202)
    - Lists: class members, undated (Box 26, Folder 203)
    - Miscellaneous: correspondence and memoranda, undated (Box 26, Folder 204)
    - Reunions, 25th, 30th, 35th: correspondence and memoranda, 1901-1911 (Box 27, Folder 205 - 209)
    - Reunions, 40th, 50th: correspondence and memoranda, 1916, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 210 - 214)
    - Reunions, 55th, 60th: lists and memoranda, 1931, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 215)
    - Yale Alumni University Fund, 1899-1900 (Box 28, Folder 216)
  - Class of 1877
    - Correspondence, 1918-1925 (Box 29, Folder 217)
    - Divinity School: class letters, 1879-1922 (Box 29, Folder 218 - 222)
  - Class of 1879
    - Correspondence, 1899-1927 (Box 30, Folder 223 - 228)
  - Class of 1880
    - Correspondence, 1907-1934 (Box 31, Folder 229 - 234)
    - Correspondence, 1925-1946 (Box 32, Folder 235 - 239)
    - Correspondence, 1880-1945 (Box 33, Folder 240 - 245)
    - Log book, 1930-1935 (Box 33, Folder 246)
    - Reunion, 10th (decennial) dinner menu, 1890 (Box 34, Folder 247)
    - Reunions, 25th, 35th, 40th, 55th Correspondence and memoranda, 1900-1935 (Box 34, Folder 248 - 251)
  - Class of 1881
    - History, undated (Box 35, Folder 252)
  - Class of 1882
    - Log book: biographical notes, correspondence, 1936-1953, 1918, 194[?] (Box 35, Folder 253)
  - Class of 1883
    - Correspondence, 1922 (Box 35, Folder 254)
    - Design for class medal, 1908 (Box 35)
  - Class of 1884
    - Correspondence: Alumni University Fund, 1890-1949 (Box 36, Folder 255 - 259)
    - Correspondence: Anniversary Fund: 25th year, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 260)
    - Correspondence: Association of Secretaries, 1910-1911 (Box 36, Folder 261)
    - Correspondence, 1914-1946 (Box 36, Folder 262)
    - Correspondence, 1914-1916 (Box 37, Folder 263 - 266)
    - Correspondence: crass book, Class Ivy, class record, 1909-1911 (Box 37, Folder 267)
    - Correspondence: Class letters from Secretary, 1919-1947 (Box 37, Folder 268)
    - Correspondence: Library Fund, 1945-1946 (Box 37, Folder 269)
    - Correspondence, 1884-1949 (Box 38, Folder 270 - 276)
    - Reunion, 6th, 25th: correspondence, memoranda, 1890-1909 (Box 39, Folder 277 - 278)
    - Reunion, 30th, 31st, 35th, 40th; 45th: correspondence and memoranda, 1914-1929 (Box 39, Folder 279)
    - Reunfon, 50th: correspondence and memoranda, 1934 (Box 39, Folder 280)
    - Reunion, 55th: correspondence and memoranda, 1939 (Box 39, Folder 281)
    - Reunion, 60th, 65th: correspondence and memoranda, 1944, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 282)
    - Statistics for Class Record (forms), 1906-1914 (Box 39, Folder 283 - 285)
    - Statistics for Class Record (forms), 1906-1914 (Box 40, Folder 286 - 290)
    - Statistics for Class Record (forms), 1906-1914 (Box 41, Folder 291 - 295)
    - War Service Record, 1915-1921 (Box 41, Folder 296)
  - Class of 1885
    - Class lists, undated (Box 42, Folder 297)
    - Correspondence, 1888-1946 (Box 42, Folder 298 - 299)
    - Speech given in Middletown, no name, 1888 January 31 (Box 42, Folder 300)
  - Class of 1887
    - Class list, undated (Box 42, Folder 301)
    - Correspondence: Alumni and Endorment Fund, 1926-1930 (Box 42, Folder 302 - 305)
    - Report of a Committee on Alumni Association Scholarships to the Yale Alumni Advisory Board, 1922 (Box 42, Folder 306)
    - Yale Alumni Fund publication, undated (Box 42, Folder 307)
    - Yale Alumni Weekly: Alumni Fund Extra, 1927 (Box 42, Folder 308)
    - Yale Endowment Fund Committee publications, 1927 (Box 42, Folder 309)
    - "Yale - Past and Present": Dean Clarence Mendell, an address delivered on Alumni Day, 1927 (Box 42, Folder 310)
  - Class of 1888
    - Correspondence, 1921-1924 (Box 42, Folder 311)
    - Minutes of a meeting of the Yale Association of Class Secretaries, 1921 (Box 42, Folder 312)
    - New York Dinner, 1925 (Box 42, Folder 313)
  - Class of 1889
    - Reunion, 20th: notice, 1909 (Box 43, Folder 314)
    - Reunion notes, 1912 (Box 43, Folder 315)
    - Reunion, 25th: class list, undated (Box 43, Folder 316)
    - Reunion, 25th: correspondence, 1914 (Box 43, Folder 317 - 324)
    - Reunion, 25th: published notes, 1914 (Box 43, Folder 325)
    - Correspondence, 1915-1918 (Box 43, Folder 326 - 327)
    - Class Dinner, 1918 (Box 43, Folder 328)
    - Reunion, 30th: banquet, meeting, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 329 - 331)
    - Reunion, 30th: correspondence, lists, notices, 1919 (Box 44, Folder 332 - 344)
    - Class Dinner, 1922 (Box 44, Folder 345)
    - Reunion, 35th: correspondence, 1924 (Box 44, Folder 346)
    - Reunion, 35th: correspondence, 1924 (Box 45, Folder 347 - 357)
    - Reunion, 40th: correspondence, 1929 (Box 45, Folder 358 - 359)
    - Reunion, 40th: correspondence, 1929 (Box 46, Folder 360 - 364)
    - Reunion, 45th: correspondence, 1934 (Box 46, Folder 365 - 368)
    - Reunion, 45th: dinner, 1934 (Box 47, Folder 369 - 371)
    - Reunion roll book, 1909-1954 (Box 47, Folder 372)
    - Photograph:" '89 Whistling to keep their courage up June 27, 1899 Harvard 4 Yale 3", 1899-06-27 (Box 47, Folder 372a)
  - Class of 1890
    - Biographical material, forms: 40th Reunion, 1931 (Box 47, Folder 373 - 374)
    - Biographical material, forms: 45th Reunion, 1936 (Box 47, Folder 375 - 376)
    - Biographical material, forms: 50th Reunion, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 377)
    - Biographical material, forms, 60th year class history, 1951 (Box 48, Folder 378)
    - Class lists, 1941-1957 (Box 48, Folder 379)
    - Correspondence, 1931-1951 (Box 48, Folder 380 - 382)
    - Correspondence, 1952-1958 (Box 49, Folder 383 - 387)
    - Notebook: biographical infomation, undated (Box 49, Folder 388)
    - Printed notices on reunions, 1936-1951 (Box 49, Folder 389)
    - Reunion, 55th: Class Dinner, speech by Secretary John Tilson, 1946 (Box 49, Folder 390)
  - Class of 1892
    - Correspondence, 1938-1954 (Box 50, Folder 391 - 393)
  - Class of 1893
    - Automobile Committee's Report: (Automobile purchased for uie of classmate Rev. Gaes F. Goodenough), 1923 (Box 50, Folder 394)
  - Class of 1894
    - "Our Class at Yale": Edward J. Redington, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 395)
    - American Field Service Certificate, 1918 (Box 50, Folder 396)
  - Class of 1895
    - Correspondence, 1940-1964 (Box 51, Folder 397 - 398)
    - Correspondence, 1906-1947 (Box 52, Folder 399 - 401)
    - Correspondence: Alumni Fund, 1912 (Box 52, Folder 402)
    - Ambulance Fund, 1919-1920 (Box 52, Folder 403)
    - Correspondence: Ambulance, gift of class to Red Cross during World War II, 1940-1945 (Box 52, Folder 404 - 406)
    - Correspondence: re ambulance. Yale Alumni Magazine and clippings, 1942-1943, 1941 (Box 53, Folder 407)
    - Correspondence: Clarence Day Memorial Room, 1936-1937 (Box 53, Folder 408 - 409)
    - Correspondence: expenses an class publications, 1911-1912 (Box 53, Folder 410)
    - Dinners and other functions: correspondence, speeches, memoranda, 1902-1929 (Box 53, Folder 411)
    - Drawings: Oviatt, Edwin, undated (Box 53, Folder 412)
    - History, 1896 (Box 53, Folder 413)
    - Memorabilia: programs, sketches, 1892-1899, undated (Box 53, Folder 414)
    - Printed material, 1904-1947 (Box 53, Folder 415)
    - Record book of scholarship, attendance and discipline records, 1892-93 (Box 54, Folder 416)
    - Register, 1921-61 (Box 54, Folder 417)
    - 20 Million Dollar Endowment Fund, 1926 (Box 54, Folder 418)
    - Reunion Speeches, 1916, 1921, 1936 (Box 54, Folder 419)
  - Class of 1897
    - Coreespondence, 1922-1957 (Box 55, Folder 420 - 428)
    - Correspondence (Box 56, Folder 429 - 432)
    - Memoriam cards, 1937-1957 (Box 56, Folder 433)
    - Miscellaneous lists, undated (Box 56, Folder 434)
    - Register, 1937 (Box 56, Folder 435)
    - Reunion, 55th: correspondence, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 436)
    - Reunions: Seaview Golf Club autumn reunions, 1937-1950 (Box 56, Folder 437)
  - Class of 1898
    - Records of the Class Day Cornittees, 1904-1909 (Box 57, Folder 438)
    - Reunion, 30th: Registers, 1929-1944 (Box 57, Folder 439)
    - American Field Service Certificate, 1918 (Box 58, Folder 440)
  - Class of 1900
    - Reunion, 6th: correspondence, 1906 (Box 58, Folder 1 - 2)
  - Class of 1901
    - Autographed guest book given to Dean Henry P. Wright at annual dinner, 1914 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1902
    - Reunion, 30th: song and poem, 1932 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Collected records of the Classes of 1903-1952, 1900-1973; Accession 19ND-A-403
  - Class of 1903
    - Annual Dinners, 1946-1949 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Association of Yale Secretaries, 1963-1964 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Check book: Vicennial Committee, 1923 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Class Fund financial statements, 1938-1965 (Box 59, Folder 8 - 11)
    - Chronological: Necrology, 1901-1966 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1963 (Box 60, Folder 13 - 17)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1963 (Box 61, Folder 18 - 22)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1963 (Box 62, Folder 23 - 28)
    - Correspondence, 1918-1929 (Box 63, Folder 29 - 33)
    - Minutes of Yale College Fund, 1965-1966 (Box 64, Folder 34)
    - Minute Book: minutes of meetings, notices, reunions, 1903-1948 (Box 64, Folder 35 - 38)
    - Sixty-year Record, 1963 (Box 64, Folder 39)
    - American Field Services Certificate, 1918 (Box 64, Folder 40)
  - Class of 1904
    - Financial records, Class Council, 1931-1965 (Box 65, Folder 41)
    - Minute Book, Class Council, 1923-1924 (Box 65, Folder 42)
    - Minute Book, Class Council, 1923-1965 (Box 65, Folder 43)
    - Ephemera, 1903-1904 (Box 65, Folder 43A)
  - Class of 1905
    - Correspondence, 1949-1965 (Box 65, Folder 44)
  - Class of 1908
    - Correspondence, 1904-1938 (Box 66, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence, 1938-1967 (Box 67, Folder 46)
    - Correspondence, 1946-1953 (Box 68, Folder 47)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1956 (Box 69, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence, 1954-1957 (Box 70, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1963 (Box 71, Folder 50)
    - Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 72, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence, 1962-1969 (Box 73, Folder 52)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1973 (Box 74, Folder 53)
    - Report of the Commission of Alumni Affairs (Box 74, Folder 54)
    - Speech presentation to Charles Seymour from classmates at dinner, 1937 (Box 74, Folder 55)
  - Class of 1910
    - Correspondence, 1910-1911 (Box 75, Folder 56)
    - Registers: reunions, 1913-1940 (Box 75, Folder 57)
    - Memorabilia, 1950 (Box 75, Folder 58)
  - Class of 1911
    - Award: Magna Cum Laude received for 40: Year Record Book, undated (Box 76, Folder 59)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1970 (Box 76, Folder 60 - 65)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1970 (Box 77, Folder 66 - 71)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1970 (Box 78, Folder 72 - 77)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1970 (Box 79, Folder 78 - 82)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1970 (Box 80, Folder 83 - 88)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1970 (Box 81, Folder 89 - 93)
    - Printed matter
      - Alumni Weekly: Commencement, reunions, 1911, 1936, 1941, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 94)
      - Class of 1911 Yale College Five Year Record, 1916 (Box 82, Folder 95)
      - Class of 1911 Yale College Decennial Record, 1922 (Box 82, Folder 96)
      - Class of 1911 Yale College Twenty Fifth Record, 1936 (Box 83, Folder 97)
      - History of the Class of 1911: Vol I (Box 83, Folder 98)
      - History of the Class of 1911: Vol V, 1952 (Box 83, Folder 99)
      - The Yale Banner and Pot Pourri, 1910-1911 (Box 84, Folder 100)
    - Miscellaneous: announcements, booklets, pamphlets, 1907-1956 (Box 84, Folder 101 - 103)
    - Reunions: attendance records and registers, 1914-1951 (Box 85, Folder 104)
    - Scrapbook from Secretary John M. Holcombe: memoranda, 1921-1951 (Box 85, Folder 105)
    - Speeches: dinners, reunions, 1951-1966 (Box 85, Folder 106)
  - Class of 1912
    - Statistics: class members question forms A-L, 1911 (Box 86, Folder 107 - 112)
    - Statistics: class members question forms M-Z, 1911 (Box 87, Folder 113 - 116)
  - Class of 1913
    - Correspondence, memoranda, clippings, 1913-1965 (Box 88, Folder 117 - 118)
  - Class of 1916
    - Reunions, 15th, 20th, 25th, 30th: correspondence, finances, history, memoranda, 1931-1946 (Box 89, Folder 119 - 122)
  - Class of 1917
    - Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 90, Folder 123)
    - Recording Tape: 50th Reunion, 1967 (Box 90, Folder 124)
    - Sound film (no description), 1927-1932 (Box 90, Folder 125)
    - Sound film: Class Dinner, 1932 (Box 90, Folder 126)
    - Sound film (no description), 1937-1952 (Box 90, Folder 127 - 128)